Aman Khandelwal

Alwar, Rajasthan, India



aman.khandelwal1205@gmail.com





linkedin.com/in/aman-khandelwal-1205

Summary

I'm Aman Khandelwal, currently pursuing B.Tech in Computer Science Engineering. I am a MERN Stack Developer and a Digital Marketer, having expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, React Native, Node Js, React Js. Moreover, I have a deep interest in Android Development as well. Other than academics, I am the Founder of a tech start-up (Software Development & Digital Marketing Company) named Flaanzo Technologies where I along with my team provide various online services which a business needs to grow.

Experience



Founder

Flaanzo Technologies

May 2020 - Present (1 year 8 months +)

Flaanzo Technologies is a start-up that has turned up in to a very successful Software Development and Digital Marketing Company. Within a very short span of 1 Year, Flaanzo Technologies has completed more than 10 successful projects, resulting in happy & long-term collaboration with our clients.

Website Frontend Developer

Tractor Junction

Dec 2020 - Sep 2021 (10 months)

The work responsibilities include the development of website front end using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript. Along with the front end, I had also handled website backend using Laravel (PHP) and my SQL database.

Education

MITRC College, Alwar

Bachelor of Technology - B.Tech, Computer Science Engineering

2019 - 2023

I'm Aman Khandelwal, pursuing B.Tech in Computer Science Engineering. I am a Website Front End Developer, Digital Marketer, and Founder of a tech start-up (IT & Digital Marketing service providing company) named Flaanzo Technologies.

Licenses & Certifications

- Server-side Development with NodeJS, Express and MongoDB
- Modern Application Development with Node.js on AWS Specialization Offered By AWS (Coursera)
- Full-Stack Web Development with React Specialization Coursera
- Introduction to Web Development with HTML, CSS, JavaScript Offered By IBM (Coursera)
- Google Digital Unlocked The Fundamental of Digital Marketing Google Digital Garage
- Google Analytics For Power User Beginners Google Analytics

Skills

- Front-End Development
- Back-End Web Development
- HTML5
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- API Development

Projects

Text Utils

Text Utils is a text utility React application that facilitates the user. to manipulate the text such as turning the text into Uppercase, Lowercase, Titlecase and remove extra spaces.

Project Link - https://amankhandelwal02.github.io/textutils/

Medi Compare

Medi Compare is an online pharma that facilitates the users to browse, buy and compare medicine based on the diseases or symptoms they have, among the different platforms available in India. This website is made with pure HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript and firebase database.

Project Link - https://amankhandelwal02.github.io/medi-compare/index.html

Notes App

This is a simple note made with complete HTML, CSS and JavaScript. The application lets the user to take some notes by adding a title and description and also deleting the notes.

Project Link - https://amankhandelwal02.github.io/notes-taking-app/